Venkata C R Challa

1285 Rumba Ln #A, Tallahassee, FL 32304

+1 551-240-9459 | cvchakradharreddy@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hellocv/

Summary

Experienced full stack web application developer with 2+ years of working in the Angular MVC Framework. Currently, looking for an internship opportunity as a full stack/front-end application developer in Summer 2018

Technical Skills

HTML5, CSS, AngularJS, JavaScript, jQuery, JAVA

Augmented Reality, Hybrid Mobile apps with Cordova and Agile Methodology

Education

Florida State University

- Master's Degree in Computer Science, GPA 3.83/4

Rajiv Gandhi University of Knowledge Technologies

May 2014

- Undergraduate Major Degree in Electronics & Communications Engr., CGPA 8.92/10
- Undergraduate Minor Degree in Computer Science and Engr., CGPA 8.24/10

Current Project

Augmented Reality mobile app

5 months

Graduate project

May 2017 – Present

Expected: Fall 2018

A social networking app that allows users to tag a memory to a real-world object in AR world.

- Created hybrid mobile app using HTML5, CSS and JavaScript
- Extensively worked with Wikitude, Cordova framework and Couchbase database

Professional Experience

UI and Java Developer

2 years, 2 months

Company: ADP Pvt. Ltd., Hyderabad, India

Nov 2014 - Dec 2016

Projects: Analytics & Reporting

- Built views/templates using HTML5, CSS and AngularJS
- Enhanced data visualization using *Highcharts JS*, *Datatables* and *Colreorder*
- Implemented Web API services using JAVA and MongoDB (for aggregations)

Web Application Developer (Intern)

3 months

Company: PITERION Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore, India

May 2013 - Jul 2013

Project: Sales web application

- Constructed front-end mechanism using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery
- Executed back-end mechanism using PHP, MySQL database

Academic Work Experience

Graduate Teaching Assistant at FSU

12 months

Duties include teaching Microsoft office tools, holding lab hours and grading assignments

Jan 2017 - Present